[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is a correct statement about the last parts of the movie The Conversation?", "correct_answer": "Anns husband is murdered by the big corporation.", "incorrect_answers": ["Anns boyfriend is murdered by the big corporation.", "Harrys girlfriend, Amy, is taken prisoner by the big corporation until he gives them the video tape he has made.", "Harry is murdered by the big corporation."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these can help produce pencils, without cutting down trees?", "correct_answer": "jeans", "incorrect_answers": ["leaves", "benches", "branches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of company did Lillian found after the death of her husband Oscar in the 1992 comedy movie Brain Donors?", "correct_answer": "Ballet company", "incorrect_answers": ["Charitable foundation", "Donor foundation", "Law firm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the common name of cecotropes, products of the cecum which rabbits reingest to get nutrients?", "correct_answer": "Night feces", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabbit pellets", "False feces", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Ritchies brother in the movie The Benchwarmers?", "correct_answer": "Howie", "incorrect_answers": ["Greg", "Hadden", "Peter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Bermuda Triangle has been responsible for the disappearances of this number of planes and ships, which have been lost till the end of the 20th century.", "correct_answer": "66", "incorrect_answers": ["78", "52", "113"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do mathematicians call a quadrilateral with exactly one pair of parallel sides?", "correct_answer": "A trapezoid", "incorrect_answers": ["A square", "A rectangle", "An ellipse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2002 movie was a remake of the 1998 Japanese film of the same name. Its success opened the door for several other Japanese film remakes.", "correct_answer": "The Ring", "incorrect_answers": ["The Grudge", "Shutter", "Dark Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Love? Above all things I believe in love! Love is like oxygen! Love is a many splendored thing, love lifts us up where we belong, all you need is love! \n(2001)", "correct_answer": "Moulin Rouge", "incorrect_answers": ["Hope Floats", "Some Like It Hot", "Casablanca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie \u201cBride of Chucky\u201d, the fourth of the Child\u2019s Play series, Chucky\u2019s girlfriend Tiffany brings Chucky back using what book about voodoo magic?", "correct_answer": "Voodoo 4 Dummies", "incorrect_answers": ["The Power of Voodoo Magic", "The Voodoo Guide 2000", "Voodoo Forever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedy troupe started Something Completely Different on BBC Channel 1 in 1969.", "correct_answer": "Monty Pythons Flying Circus", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscar Alices Comedy Revue", "Arsenic and Old Laces", "The Benny Hill Show"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the first iron bridge built?", "correct_answer": "Coalbrookdale, England", "incorrect_answers": ["Milton, Massachusetts", "Paris, France", "Brussels, Belgium"]}]